[Music]
are we
rolling we are currently here on site
with Bart to mon of Dresden standing
just outside wi Wonka's chocolate
factory just last week the world
renowned chocolate maker sent out five
golden tickets for five lucky children
to find and the one who makes it through
to the end earns themselves a very
special prize so Bart we have to ask do
you feel any amount of guilt for buying
all of the chocolate bars in the world
guaranteeing all five golden tickets
only for you and your small group of
friends not at all I earned my money and
I have the right to do whatever the hell
I want with it those 8-year-old kids who
wanted to participate but couldn't
because of me I consider that a skill
issue on their end I couldn't have said
it bitter myself any minute now Mr Wonka
will open the doors and Bart Toby and
his friends will enter the Chocolate
Factory and meet the candy maker himself
look everybody the doors are opening oh
my God it's finally happening
[__] B Be I I think I see
him how look he's playing with us like
we are kids that's so funny come on out
now WKA we all know you
there no way it's the one and only
Timothy
[Applause]
shoman Mom it's Wily Wonka himself I
don't believe it is the factory really
mine Bartleby he only if you win [__]
only if you
win welcome my friends Welcome to My
Chocolate Factory will the ones who
found my five golden tickets please step
forward haha well three tickets in one
how household you must be very lucky
hedgehogs luck had nothing to do with it
Sonic really likes candy so B will be
bought out your whole
stock [__] everyone with a brand new
bar be would do that and for the record
chicks are supposed to wait at the back
of the line now the rest of you follow
me wait a sec you are not even the real
Willy WKA no yes I am I'm just a shitty
one no offense but we were just to meet
Johnny
Depp nobody even knows who that
is that's okay old sport I'll take it
from here but you said children need a
guardian with them this is my nephew Hey
kid do you want to come inside and see
my chocolate factory or do you want to
stay with your grumpy old fle I think
the answer is awfully clear if you ask
me I want to go with you Mr wonger you
you are a
kidnapper you belong in prison with the
rest of your kind when I get home I am
going to email people so they
know room to Loop US Open the doors
we're
coming
well everyone Feast your eyes this is my
candy factory everything you see here is
made of candy this is the prize one of
you shall win if you can make it through
the entire tour now go out there and
explore I just have two rules one don't
bother theopus as they are hard at work
look B this bush over here is growing
your favorite tens of spam oh Mr Wonka
this is a dream come true for a boy like
me that that weighs only 35 lb can I
really eat all of it of course in fact
Sonic I planted that spam push just for
you because I knew deep in my heart that
you would win one of my golden tickets
as well as my
factory now after you eat your spam go
have fun but whatever you do don't touch
the chocolate
River let's just say it might not
exactly be the pleasant experience you
would expect it to be oh ho ho I think I
get what you mean Mr wonger it's not
awate at all it's a who love your own
backed up [__] well guess what it's
going down my goet tons of spam rivers
of poop and now grape soda pop one car
is there anything you can't
do Charles I think we should
leave for some reason I can't shake the
feeling that this place is sort of
[__] up Al
oh so you like gumballs H manic you
calling me a fruit loop you son of a
[__] it does sort to look like my
flabby nut sag how would you like to
taste a very special gun ball is it one
of your weird sex things a little bit
wow oh Sonic I see you already found it
the most secret candy in my entire
Factory I it over there behind the giant
candy toilet that theopus used to empty
their butt
into have you tasted it yet I was just
about to so good then we can all
experience this moment together what's
the big deal is it not just a dainty big
white ball of sweetness much like my own
I'm glad you asked Bar B cause this big
white ball has a very unique property
you see it has no flavor by itself
rather it carries the the flavor of the
salty ball sack of the last person to
hold it it is the only candy that ever
made that surpasses the Everlasting God
stoer you did it Mr Wonka you did
it give me those
balls oh my God doing
it well how was it darling W you are a
mad genius don't than me the Impalas are
the ones who get a little frisky after
lights out I think they're
homosexual some kid is drinking from the
alate
river way from there the way from there
I say don't you realize you're
contaminating my entire load of w k bars
with Your Filthy
Hands load I'll give you a [__] load
you [__]
[Music]
idiot
I got him in my sights bit should I take
the
shot godamn it use iconic orange PP he's
just a
boy if a boy is old enough to dream he's
old enough to die hold me fire until I
say so and return to the cotton candy
field no think about where you are right
now from this position I'm the one who
makes the rules this um paluma with a
booty is done taking orders from a man
named Willie you know the name Willie is
nickname for men's chitalia don't you
man I bet you were buied as a kid oh
well I guess it's better than my own
birth name booty bad on
on everyone hide one of myal loas have
gone Rogue
again B what are you going to do with
that
licorish what Bartle be used the candy
to make a Bolis the Primitive hunting
weapon we're saved it's not over yet
Sony the time to earn our rights have
come the oala prising begins
today Willie why are they doing this to
us I thought you treated your workers
with love and care do you even pay them
why would I they have a different skin
color so you treat them like trash
because they look different than you I
do not treat them like [__] I gave 341
of them a whole 6X 8T bedroom to share
everyone flee from your lives because
I'm not raising their
pay run the oal loas can't catch people
who run since they are short oh how
sweet the Blom power pulling a get out
of the chocolate River to save his
life that's weird why are they taking
off his pants wait he just punch an
Bloom thigh in the balls oh my God and
now he's the one raping them oh my
god
[Music]
without fizzy lifting drinks hey Uncle
Chuck what do you think this will do why
drink it and F
Uncle Chuck look at me I'm floating like
a
[Music]
balloon no way I'm flying all the way to
the
Moon I can't Uncle Chuck it must be
something to do with that fizzy soda I
just
[Music]
trank except
is yeah now that you mention it we
should probably grab something to pull
ourselves down so we don't get shredded
to Pieces well
I
am I just love seeing an uncle and
nephew get along oh there's nothing to
grab on to H Sonia manic fart bit fart
if you fart the Fizz will vanished from
your body and you will float downward it
is the only
[Music]
way it worked Uncle Chuck Hur you do it
do
indeed I'll bet this room is going to be
super smelly after you let out all that
gas and I'm [__] here for
it
hey help meic help I can't Uncle I've
fallen to far it's
last faite NF
Doom look Uncle Chuck everyone else is
leaving the factory though I'm so happy
we were all able to make it out save
fans
[Music]
sound and him for giving us this
wonderful
[Music]
experience no it's just you what do you
want tur I was wondering when I was
going to get my prize you know the
factory my Factory what made you think I
was giving away my house the price was
$14 the choice between one Chon's
Brothers concerning New York or 32 Drake
compan concerts in Mexico and you won't
even get that because you stole fizy
lifting
[Music]
drinks
concert what Domingo you think you you
see I'm something of a magician and
inventor and chocolate maker so quiet up
and listen down nope scratch that
reverse it I'm just a
rapist get my elevator time to escape in
my Wonka Glass
Elevator your days are numbered Sonic
Hedgehog no you don't you're not taking
him anywhere without
me damn it's the only man who is capable
of catching me bar how did you find us
I'm not going to tell you it's over Wily
so stop actually I'm glad you could make
it do you know why why don't we speak
theatrics and C to the chase very well
this elevator can't go anywhere I want
up left right down and right now we are
leaving my factory because we're flying
towards the Grand Canyon where I'm going
to drop you in a volcano and kill you
both you fool would that not only kill
you as well on the contrary I had my own
pupus installed this glass chair to the
wall so when the bottle floor panel
opens up I will be sitting safe and
sound it's unfortunate the same couldn't
be said for the
lovers you're a cruel terrible man will
surely hell will welcome a man like you
when you meet God tell him he can suck
my everlasting God
[Music]
stoer
it feels good to be king Man Sonic
Underground mons time to watch Modern
Sonic on my portable cell phone and then
I'll return to the factory and Quil the
unaloon P
pricing huh well Bach I believe it's
about time to show everyone what you've
been packing away back
there
a fizzy lifting drink stop it stop it
now don't you come near my glass
elevator that was quite check you little
one taking that fizzy lifting drink like
that you naughty boy yes but how will we
ever get home we're in the middle of the
Grand
Canyon oh it appears someone showed up
to give us a ride sweet the Ooma loomas
have come to take home oh no they ain't
but look again they're packing
mags actually maybe a high C on foot
doesn't sound so bad after all I always
did want to see the Grand Canyon well
now you did [__] we both
[Music]
did 15 minutes this epod Saka [__]
sucked
[Music]
w